<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vish</title>
    <link>https://vishalnarayan.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Vish</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 23:53:44 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://vishalnarayan.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>https://vishalnarayan.github.io/posts/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 23:53:44 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vishalnarayan.github.io/posts/test/</guid>
      <description>Hi there! This is a test page and will be removed shortly so enjoy it while you can.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malai Rigatoni</title>
      <link>https://vishalnarayan.github.io/food/malai-rigatoni/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 23:49:42 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vishalnarayan.github.io/food/malai-rigatoni/</guid>
      <description>This is the dish inspired by Pijja Palace.
Got the recipe from The Global Vegetarian.
The recipe on this page is just for the sauce. Cooking the pasta is pretty self-explanatory.
Ingredients 2 tbsp butter 1 tbsp olive oil 2 bay leaves 1 small red onion, finely chopped 8-10 cloves garlic, minced 1.5 tomatoes, finely chopped 2/3 cup tomato paste 1.5 tsp red chili powder 1-2 tsp red chili flakes 1/4 tsp turmeric 3/4 tsp cumin powder 1/4 tsp cardamom powder 1/2 tsp coriander powder salt to taste 1/4 cup vodka 1/4 tsp pepper 1/4 tsp sugar 1 cup heavy cream (can sub coconut milk) 3 tbsp chopped basil 3 tbsp chopped coriander Cook Pan on low-medium heat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rasam</title>
      <link>https://vishalnarayan.github.io/food/rasam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 23:49:38 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vishalnarayan.github.io/food/rasam/</guid>
      <description>Rasam Prep 1/3 cup toor dal 1 tbsp tamarind paste roughly 5 sprigs curry leaves 1-2 tomatoes, chopped or quartered 1-2 tsp each of asafoetida, turmeric This ratio of spices = 1 red chilli powder : 1.5 coriander : 2 cumin : 1 black pepper. How much of each you add is based on personal preference. Mine is at least 3 tsp of rcp. cilantro, chopped The measurements of spices here are ultimately based on personal preference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Shawarma</title>
      <link>https://vishalnarayan.github.io/food/chicken-shawarma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 23:49:14 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vishalnarayan.github.io/food/chicken-shawarma/</guid>
      <description>Marinade 8 garlic cloves 1 shallot 6 tbsp olive oil 2 tbsp cumin 2 tbsp coriander 1 tbsp sumac 1 tsp paprika 1 tsp turmeric 1 tsp allspice 1 tsp ground ginger 1/2 tsp cinnamon 1/2 tsp cardamom 2 1/2 tsp salt add yogurt as desired Cook Preheat oven to 400 degrees F. Cook chicken for roughly 20 minutes, flipping halfway through. Heat up a skillet, add olive oil, and sear/cook the chicken as desired.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dummypage</title>
      <link>https://vishalnarayan.github.io/chess/dummypage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 23:47:37 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vishalnarayan.github.io/chess/dummypage/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the chess index.
Here, I will have links to opening theory, concepts, educational games, and more.
For now, putting everything here.
Opening Lines 1. e4 e5 Scotch e4 e5 Nf3 Nc6 d4 exd4 Nxd4 Here, black can continue with Nf6 or Bc5. Bc5 White can continue with Be3, Nb3, or Nxc6 Be3 Qf6 Here, Qf6 is a good system, with Ne7 following. Another move is Bb6. At this point if Nxc6, then Bxe3 threatens mate and is good for black.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Chettinad</title>
      <link>https://vishalnarayan.github.io/food/chicken-chettinad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 23:39:50 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vishalnarayan.github.io/food/chicken-chettinad/</guid>
      <description>Following the recipe from this youtube video.
Marinade 1/2 tsp turmeric powder 1 tbsp lemon juice few pinches of salt This is for rougly 1lb chicken. Adjust proportions as necessary.
Chettinad Masala 3 tbsp coriander seeds 6 dried red chillis 1 tbsp black pepper 1 tsp cumin seeds 1 tsp fennel seeds 1 green cardamom 1 black cardamom (just use extra green if you don&amp;#39;t have these) 1 star anise 8 cloves 1 inch piece cinnamon 2 black stone flowers 1 blade of mace 6-8 cloves garlic 1 inch ginger 1 tsp tamarind paste pinch of fenugreek seeds Heat up 1 tbsp of sesame oil in a pan.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
